[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Air is good.
We have a working relationship.
Okay.
I'm pretty sure nobody followed me
in here, so I've got that going for me.
I have supply concerns about the
air in this room, though.
Business needs to expand.
We need more investors, which I
guess would be plants?
NOT WORMS!
Worms are not conducive to good business.
Look at this. They're trying to
take over the market.
I need to withdraw.
I'm taking my assets with me
and I'm going to look for
business opportunities elsewhere.
[underwater panicking]
[underwater mumbling]
[gasping]
This is a tight market.
No matter.
Here at Freeman Industries, we
practice sound investment strategies.
[underwater mumbling]
Okay, don't panic,
don't panic, don't panic.
I'm sure there's minutes' worth
of air in this pocket.
PANIC!
[underwater mumbling]
[Right?  No, left!  Left!]
[gasping, coughing]
Oh.
Jee-yaah, ooh...
Wow, I wouldn't have thought
this was the right way.
I'm wet.
Blehblugh!
I wonder if there are places
that do amphibious pizza delivery.
Like by the beach or something.
Damn, I'm kind of hungry, huh?
It's all this swimming.
And beating things to death with a crowbar.
I should've brought some
more snacks with me.
[ichthyosaur roars, scientist screams]
Well, I'm not the only one who's hungry!
Jesus Christ!
Do we keep sharks down here?
Sharks!
What the f...
Ah, hold on.  I need to tidy
this place up a bit.
Yuck...
Come to think of it, how much do
I really know about Black Mesa?
We have toxic waste, loads of weapons,
missiles, and now a shark tank.
Am I working for a
James Bond villain company?
I mean, I don't really care, but...
Oh ho!
I don't even know who's
in charge here...
I bet it's some bald guy with a
scar on his face stroking a cat.
Just watching security cameras all day.
We're probably trying to take over
the world and I don't even know it.
What's that say?
Scientist: Did you see--
JESUS CHRIST!  I would've shot you!
SCIENTIST:  --from the Challenger Deep.
SCIENTIST: But I'm positive that beast never
swam in terrestrial waters until a week ago.
It's a shark.
SCIENTIST:  There's a tranquilizer
gun in the shark cage,
SCIENTIST: but I'm not sure
What?
SCIENTIST: it would work on this species.
SCIENTIST: You're welcome to try.
Thanks, but I have a real gun.
Tranquilizer... look, I appreciate
wanting to preserve the specimen
in the name of science, but if
that thing gets out of line,
I'm blowing its frigging head off.
Oh, and hey, if
anybody else comes by here,
I need you to be a
character witness for me.
Don't fuck me on this.
Now, what's this say?
I can't read this at all...
These look like my old notes when I would
show up to class drunk back in grad school.
That was pretty sweet.
I could get piss drunk most nights
Then hook up an IV to my arm
with a saline solution
and not wake up hung over.
I would just have a buzz instead.
It was awesome having a
med student as a roommate.
Hey, wait, what am I thinking?
That guy said there's animal tranquilizer.
I can get high off of that.
I mean, it's pretty crazy stuff, but
these are crazy times!
Yeah, I don't think that shark
could jump this high.
Or, can he?
I don't know, better safe than sorry.
Where is he?
Ah!
[ichthyosaur moans]
Yeah!
I killed the shark!
Okay, here we go.
Okay...
Alright, let's take a look.
Dammit, that thing's still alive.
Ah, I don't care.
What's this dart say?
10ccs...
What the hell?
This is Xylazine!
I can't get high off of this!
God dammit!
RARGH!
[underwater panicking]
[ichthyosaur growls]
[crunch]
[barnacle chirping, Gordon choking]
[underwater panicking]
[ichthyosaur growling, crunch]
[gasping]
Go, go, GO, GO!
Aah!  Oh my God!
FUCK YOU, FISH!
Oh, it is on!
You wanna eat me?
I'll give you something to eat.
You think I work at Sea World?
Giving you free food all day?
You're gonna have to pay for this meal.
Come on up, I won't hurt you.
Come on up.
Sucker.
[ichthyosaur gurgles]
YEAH!
CALL ME ISHMAEL, BITCH!
Stupid shark...
That takes some of the fight out of you?
Oh!  Almost forgot about you!
Oop, need to reload.
[whistles "Blow the Man Down"]
Looks like I cleaned everything up.
I am a bad ass pool boy.
This water still looks nasty, though.
But I'm not going back.
[underwater humming "Blow the Man Down"]
Okay, more pull ups.
Man, I'm going to be ripped after today.
Now I need to hit the clubs more than ever.
Hell, maybe I still can.
If I get out of state, the feds aren't
going to be looking for me in night clubs.
I'll drive to Dallas.  There's bound to
be something popping there.
Oh, what the hell is this?
Strangle Juncture.
Well, I'm not getting to Dallas
tonight, that's for damned sure.